VIGNESHWARI.M



+91-73588 24615



vigneshwari7991gmail.com

PROFILE

To succeed in an environment of growth and excellence IT professional with over 2 years of development experience. Highly adept at creating and maintaining curricula and programs used to train employees while effectively communicating with company personnel. Looking for a new position to develop and grow my career further.

SKILLS

- Storyline 360
- Illustrator
- MS Office
- Vyond
- After effects
- Power point

EXPERIENCE

HUMAN RESOURCES ADMIN

Varahi consulting solutions inc

Jun 2023 - Present

E-LEARNING DEVELOPER & INSTRUCTIONAL DESIGNER

Geniies IT & Services Private Limited

Oct 2021 - Feb 2023

PROCESS EXECUTIVE (RESIDENTIAL & COMMERCIAL)

Park Intelli Solutions Private Limited Jan 2020 – March 2021

EDUCATION

MA ECONOMICS (BANKING AND INSURANCE)

PSG college of arts and science, (An Autonomous institution, Affliated to Bharathiar University)

2017-2018

INSURANCE MANAGEMENT

Global Vision, Coimbatore.

2015-2016

BA ECONOMICS (BANKING AND INSURANCE)

PSGR Krishnammal College for womens, (An Autonomous institution, Affliated to Bharathiar University)

2014 - 2017

PORTFOLIO LINK

https://www.behance.net/vigneshwari 7991